let questions = [
  // {
  //   num: 1,
  //   question: "What does HTML stands for?",
  //   answer: "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. Hyper Type Multi Language",
  //     "B. Hyper Text Multi Language",
  //     "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
  //     "D. Home Text Multi Language",
  //   ],
  // },
  // {
  //   num: 2,
  //   question: "What CSS stand for?",
  //   answer: "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
  //     "B. Cute Style Sheet",
  //     "C. Computer Style Sheet",
  //     "D. Counting Style Sheet",
  //   ],
  // },

  // {
  //   num: 3,
  //   question: "What does PHP stand for?",
  //   answer: "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
  //     "B. Hometext Programming",
  //     "C. Hypertext Preprogramming",
  //     "D. Programming Hypertext Preprocessor",
  //   ],
  // },
  // {
  //   num: 4,
  //   question: "What does SQL stand for?",
  //   answer: "D. Structured Query Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. Strength Query Language",
  //     "B. Stylesheet Query Language",
  //     "C. Science Query Language",
  //     "D. Structured Query Language",
  //   ],
  // },
  // {
  //   num: 5,
  //   question: "What does XML stand for?",
  //   answer: "D. Extensible Markup Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. Excellent Multiple Language",
  //     "B. Explore Multiple Language",
  //     "C. Extra Markup language",
  //     "D. Extensible Markup Language",
  //   ],
  // },

     
  {
      num: 1,
      question: "Who is called a companion of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
      answer: "A. A companion is one who saw the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) and believed in him and died as a Muslim",
      options: [
        "A. A companion is one who saw the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) and believed in him and died as a Muslim",
        "B. A companion is one who is a Muslim in a modern era",
        "C. All Muslims are considered as companions",
        "D. No one is a companion",
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 2,
      question: "Which of the companions did Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) state as the person who accepted Islam without even a little hesitation?",
      answer: "D. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq",
      options: [
        "A. Omar Bin Al-Khattab",
        "B. Ali Bin Abu Talib",
        "C. Uthman Bin Affan",
        "D. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq",
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 3,
      question: "Who is the fourth of the rightly-guided Caliph after the life of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
      answer: "C. Ali Bin Abu Talib",
      options: [
        "A. Uthman Bin Affan",
        "B. Omar Bin Al-Khattab",
        "C. Ali Bin Abu Talib",
        "D. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq",
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 4,
      question: "Which of the companions was a paternal uncle of the Prophet, and was considered as a strong personality both in character and in physique?",
      answer: "A. Abu Talib",
      options: [
        "A. Abu Talib",
        "B. Hamzah lbn Abdul Muttalib",
        "C. Abdul Muttalib",
        "D. None of the above"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 5,
      question: "How many of the companions have been promised paradise?",
      answer: "C. Ten",
      options: [
        "A. One thousand",
        "B. One hundred",
        "C. Ten",
        "D. One"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 6,
      question: "Which companion of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) is called “The Possessor of Two Lights”?",
      answer: "C. Uthman Bin Affan",
      options: [
        "A. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq",
        "B. Ali Bin Abu Talib",
        "C. Uthman Bin Affan",
        "D. Omar Bin Al-Khattab"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 7,
      question: " Which of the companions did Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) enjoin the responsibility of Adhan, the person who called out Adhan standing atop the Kaabah?",
      answer: "B. Bilal Ibn Rabah",
      options: [
        "A. Ammar Ibn Yasser",
        "B. Bilal Ibn Rabah",
        "C. Abdullah Ibn Masood",
        "D. None of the above"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 8,
      question: "Who were considered as the closest companions of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
      answer: "A. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq and Omar Bin Al-Khatab",
      options: [
        "A. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq and Omar Bin Al-Khatab",
        "B. Abdullah Ibn Masood and Abdullah Ibn Umar",
        "C. Abdulrahman Ibn Awuf and Bilal Ibn Rabah",
        "D. Khalid Ibn Al-Waleed and Salman Al-Faresy"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 9,
      question: "Of which companion did the Prophet say, “If there was to be a Prophet after Me, it would have been you”?",
      answer: "D. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq",
      options: [
        "A. Omar Bin Al-Khatab",
        "B. Uthman Bin Affan",
        "C. Ali Bin Abu Talib",
        "D. Abu Bakr Al-Siddiq"
      ],
    },

    {
      num: 10,
      question: "Who is the first martyr in Islam?",
      answer: "D. Khadeejah",
      options: [
        "A. Sumayyah",
        "B. Fathima",
        "C. Ayesha",
        "D. Khadeejah"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 11,
      question: "What is the single most important message from Allah that all the messengers brought?",
      answer: "B. The most important message was to worship Allah alone and none else",
      options: [
        "A. The most important message was to eat, drink and to remain happy",
        "B. The most important message was to worship Allah alone and none else",
        "C. The most important message was to worship all idols and deities",
        "D. The most important message was that they were messengers of Allah"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 12,
      question: " Who is the last Messenger of Allah?",
      answer: "C. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Jesus (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet Moses (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 13,
      question: "Who has Allah mentioned in the Quran as the best example to follow?",
      answer: "A. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "B. Pharaoh",
        "C. Angels",
        "D. Jinn"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 14,
      question: "Which prophet has been mentioned in the Quran as a friend of Allah?",
      answer: "C. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Jesus (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet Moses (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 15,
      question: "To which prophet did Allah order to build an ark?",
      answer: "B. Prophet Noah (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Jesus (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Noah (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet David (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 16,
      question: "How many prophets are mentioned in the Quran?",
      answer: "D. 25",
      options: [
        "A. 29",
        "B. 28",
        "C. 26",
        "D. 25"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 17,
      question: "To which prophet did Allah directly speak to?",
      answer: "D. Prophet Moses (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Jesus (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet David (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet Moses (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 18,
      question: "Who has been sent as a mercy to the worlds?",
      answer: "B. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Jesus (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet Moses (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet Abraham (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 19,
      question: "Which of the prophets were ordered by Allah to build the Kaabah in Makkah?",
      answer: "D. Prophet Abraham (PBUH) and Prophet Ishmael (PBUH)",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Adam (PBUH) and Prophet Noah (PBUH)",
        "B. Prophet Jesus (PBUH) and Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "C. Prophet Moses (PBUH) and Prophet David (PBUH)",
        "D. Prophet Abraham (PBUH) and Prophet Ishmael (PBUH)"
      ],
    },
    {
      num: 20,
      question: "Which prophet was born miraculously without the intervention of a man?",
      answer: "D. Prophet Jesus (PBUH) son of Mary",
      options: [
        "A. Prophet Abraham",
        "B. Prophet Moses",
        "C. Prophet Noah",
        "D. Prophet Jesus (PBUH) son of Mary"
      ],
    },
];
